过度自信。反直觉的是，有时候正是过度自信会挡住一个人的路。
Overconfidence. Counterintuitively, it's sometimes overconfidence that gets in a
你习惯了快速做事带来的正向反馈，
person's way. You're used to the positive rewards of doing things quickly and
独立完成，比如代数方程、成交率很高的销售报告，或者
independently, an algebraic equation, a sales report with a high closing rate, a
因为你擅长自己的工作，所以你可以忽略某些细节。
dissertation. Because you're good at what you do, you can skip over certain details.
然而，如果你试图匆匆说英语，最终会跳过
However, if you try to rush through speaking English, you'll end up skipping
关键细节。此外，如果你只依靠自己对口音的判断，
crucial details. Furthermore, if you only rely on your own judgment about your
尤其是基于拼写的判断，就会偏离目标。那该怎么办？
accent, particularly if it's spelling-based, short of the mark. What to do
从零开始，有意识地努力摆脱你的
about it? Start from scratch and make a conscious effort to get rid of your
放下成见，让自己处在一无所知的位置。
preconceptions. Put yourself in the position of knowing nothing about
发音、语调、音质、词语连接等。
pronunciation, intonation, voice quality, word connections, etc. Then lay the
用基础声音和节奏打好地基。再用你辛苦学来的
foundation with basic sounds and rhythms. Rebuild a new strong structure using the
语法和词汇，重建一个新的、坚固的结构。
grammar and vocab you've worked so hard to acquire.